- Were you trying to impress Penny?
- No, no, not at all.
(Leonard:)A little bit.
How did that work out for you?
(Penny(entering):)Leonard, ready to go?
Libido, one. Truth, zero.
I'm gonna ask one more time.
(Leonard:)We did the work together,
let's present the paper together.
(Sheldon:)And I'm telling you for the last time,
it's pandering, it's undignified, and bite me.
(Leonard:)Let's go.
- Bye, Sheldon.
- Goodbye, Penny.
[GRUNTS]
One of these days: Phew!
(Penny:)There you go.
(Leonard:)You're right, this side does look better.
(Penny:)No, no, I didn't say better,
I said less stained.
(Howard:)I just checked the house.
There's probably 20, 25 people in there.
- You're kidding.
- Is that all?
All? In particle physics, 25 is Woodstock.